A Finding Aid to the Garry Knox Bennett Papers, 1917-2017, bulk 1960-2017, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Garry Knox Bennett papers
1917-2017
bulk 1960-2017
Archives of American Art
Bennett, Garry Knox, 1934-
AAA.benngarr
Archival Resource Key
12.4 Linear feet
0.446 Gigabytes
The papers of woodworker, sculptor, and furniture designer Garry Knox Bennett measure 12.4 linear feet, 0.446 gigabytes, and date from 1917 to 2017 with the bulk of the material dating from 1960 to 2017. The collection documents the artist's life and career through biographical materials, correspondence with family and friends including other artists, exhibition files, professional files, financial and legal records, and printed material and scrapbooks recording his exhibition history and more, including photographs from his youth.
Biographical / Historical
Garry Knox Bennett (1934-2022) was a woodworker, sculptor, and furniture designer in Oakland, California.
Bennett was born in Alameda, California to Katherine von Tagen and Robert Bennett, but was raised by his grandparents. He attended the California College of the Arts, then the California College of Arts and Crafts, where he studied painting and began experimenting with metals. During this time he married his wife Sylvia.
He opened a studio in the late 1960s where he produced his famous roach clips, then later opened a larger studio named Squirkenworks in Oakland. In the 1970s, he began working with wood and on 1980 fabricated his infamous Nail Cabinet, a wood cabinet with a single nail driven through the face of the door, which garnered attention not only for Bennett's expert craftsmanship but also for what some saw as disrespect for the craft. Regardless of any controversy Bennett's work created, he became highly respected as a craftsman. In step with his unconventional nature, Bennett exhibited and sold his paintings and jewelry using the pseudonyms Ambrose Pillphister and Gerraldo Bennucci.
Bennett received the Award of Distinction from the Furniture Society and the Master of the Medium Award from the James Renwick Alliance, and was a Fellow of the American Craft Council. A major retrospective, Made in Oakland: The Furniture of Garry Knox Bennett, took place in 2001 at the American Craft Museum in New York and the Oakland Museum in California.
Bennett died unexpectedly in 2022 in Oakland, California.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 8 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1917-2009 (0.8 linear feet; Boxes 1, 13, OV 14)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1955-2017 (2.0 linear feet, 0.174 gigabytes; Boxes 1-3, ER0001-ER0002)
Series 3: Exhibition Files, 1979-2017 (1.4 linear feet; Boxes 3-4)
Series 4: Professional Files, 1959-2017 (5.0 linear feet, 0.272 gigabytes; Boxes 4-9, ER0003-ER0004)
Series 5: Made in Oakland: The Furniture of Garry Knox Bennett Retrospective, circa 1977-2009 (1.5 linear feet; Boxes 9-11)
Series 6: Financial and Legal Records, 1950s-2010 (0.5 linear feet; Boxes 11-12)
Series 7: Printed Materials, 1960-2015 (0.8 linear feet; Box 12)
Series 8: Scrapbooks, 1948-1997 (0.4 linear feet; Boxes 12-13)
Scope and Contents
The papers of woodworker, sculptor, and furniture designer Garry Knox Bennett measure 12.4 linear feet, 0.446 gigabytes, and date from 1917 to 2017 with the bulk of the material dating from 1960 to 2017.
The collection includes biographical materials containing Bennett's birthday and wedding celebration material, appointment calendars, childhood artwork, sketches and patterns for projects, photographs and notes regarding the Bennetts' marriage, resumes, student records, and material regarding the Bennetts' house fire in 2003. Correspondence is with artists Wendell Castle and Nancy Jurs, June Schwarcz, Kay Sekimachi and Bob Stocksdale, Albert Paley who describes an accident that occurred in 2002, and good friend and writer Jack Marlowe, as well as with wife Sylvia and daughter Jessica. Exhibition files consist of artwork price lists, artist statements, shipping documents, correspondence, and printed materials for Bennett's solo and group exhibitions. They also include documentation of a few exhibitions showing pieces from his personal art collection.
Professional files relate to workshops, lectures, exhibitions, donations, and grant proposals. Also found are project and publication files, artist statements written by Jack Marlowe and Tom Farber for Bennett, studio visit records, a video recording of an interview with Bennett, and a few digital recordings. The Made in Oakland: The Furniture of Garry Knox Bennett (2001) retrospective files consist of correspondence, fundraising records, lender files, and material regarding the creation of a book that also served as the catalog for the exhibition. Financial and legal records contain check registers, invoices and receipts, card files containing sales information, and legal material relating to the estate of Peter T. Joseph. Printed materials include clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and exhibition history material. Additional printed material can be found in the scrapbooks recording exhibitions and Bennett's career. The scrapbooks also include some personal items such as letters, photographs, and documents from Bennett's youth.
Handwritten notes by Sylvia Bennett, offering additional history and context, can be found throughout the collection. The notes were typically written onto the original folders which have been preserved along with the related material.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Garry Knox Bennett papers were donated in 2003 by Sylvia Bennett, Bennett's wife, and in 2017 by Garry Knox Bennett. The papers were collected as part of the Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project For Craft and Decorative Arts in America.
Related Materials
Also found in the Archives of American Art is an oral history interview with Garry Knox Bennett conducted February 1-2, 2002 by Glenn Adamson in Oakland, C.A. for the Archives of American Art's Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America.
Drawings; Interviews; Scrapbooks; Video recordings; American studio craft movement; Sculptors -- California -- Oakland; Woodworkers -- California -- Oakland; Furniture designers -- California -- Oakland; Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America; Castle, Wendell, 1932-2018; Stocksdale, Kay Sekimachi; Schwarcz, June, 1918-2015; Paley, Albert; Jurs, Nancy, 1941
- Biographical Materials, 1917-2009; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 1, 13, OV 14
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains wedding anniversary and birthday celebration plans, appointment calendars, notes and photographs documenting Bennett's marriage history, personal photographs of Bennett's family and friends, photographs of Bennett working with Wendell Castle on a collaboration project, and student and childhood records. Files of artwork include childhood drawings, notes with doodles and cartoons to Bennett's wife Sylvia, and sketches and patterns for woodworking projects. In 2003, the Bennett's home caught fire endangering their vast collection of artworks, some of which were designated to be exhibited at the inaugural exhibition of the San Francisco Museum of Craft Design, Dovetailing Art and Life: The Bennett Collection. The file for the Bennett's house fire consists of photographs of their damaged home and thank you letters to members of the fire department.
  - 1996 Bennett Family Update, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 25th Wedding Anniversary Plans, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 50th Birthday Cards, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 60th Birthday Party Sculpture Gift Plans, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 75th Birthday Party, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Calendars, 1971-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
    3 calendars
  - Artwork, Painting of Duck, circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Artwork, Drawing of Moby Dick, circa 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Artwork, Drawings and Sketches, circa 1966-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes some sketches and patterns for woodworking and sculpture projects.
  - Artwork, Sketches and Patterns for Projects, circa 1980s-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 14)
  - Award Ribbon, College Avenue Fall Art Fair, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Childhood Records, 1944-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Diploma, Alameda High School, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - House Fire, Photographs and Thank You Letters to Fire Department, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Marriage History, 1917-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographic Materials, circa 1950-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Includes photographs and photocopies of Bennett, Bennett and Wendell Castle working on a collaboration project, and work by Robert Dunlop.
  - Resumes, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Student Records, California College of Arts and Crafts, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1955-2017; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Boxes 1-3; 0.174 Gigabytes ER0001-ER0002
  Correspondence is with artists includes Wendell Castle and Nancy Jurs, June Schwarcz, Kay Sekimachi and Bob Stocksdale, Albert Paley who describes an accident that occurred in 2002, and good friend and writer Jack Marlowe. Other correspondence is with colleagues, curators, collectors, students, and other associates discussing various activities. Family correspondence includes letters from Bennett's daughter Jessica, as well as postcards and letters between Bennett and his wife Sylvia. Some files, particularly for artists, may include printed material.
  - A, 1985-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Australian Colleagues, 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Includes letters with Alan Wilson and Ondrej Mares.
  - B, 1962-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bagley, John and Marshall Crossman, 1985-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Benson, Benjamin, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bennucci, Gerraldo, Letters to, 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Gerraldo Bennucci was one of the pseudonyms used by Bennett.
  - Bergman, Andrew, 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bessie, Alvah, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bloomfield, Greg, 1984-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bourne, Agnes, 1988-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bowman Family, 1991-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Boyle, Peter and Loraine, 1979-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Buck, Andy, 2000-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - C, 1986-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Callahan, Gordon, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Carnegie Museum of Art, 1999-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Carniglia, Jerry, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Carpenter, Art, 2006-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Castle, Wendell and Nancy Jurs, 1982-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35-36)
  - Cearley, Guy, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Clark, Kay Barnett, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Clerico, Stephen, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Clippinger, Todd, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Coady, Judy, 1985-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cooper, Michael, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cornwells, Michael and Diane, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - D, 1988-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Daley, Bill, 1998-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Danto, Arthur and Barbara Westman, 1991-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Davis, John, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Deese, Rupert, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Denton, Colette, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Dunn, Stan and Lynda, 2004-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - E, 2004-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Eagle, Leatrice, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Edwards, JoAnn Tercera Gallery, 2002-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ellsworth, David, 1983-circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Elsesser, Sylvia and Eric, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Erickson, Robert, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Eriksmoen, Ashley, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Includes a letter of recommendation written by Bennett.
  - F, 1990-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Family, 1964-circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Includes letters between Bennett and wife Sylvia and letters from his daughter Jessica.
  - Farber, Thomas, 1989-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Fernandez-Veraud, Alejandro, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Foat, Rueben, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Fredell, Gail, circa 1997-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - G, 1960-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gaxiola, Garry (Maestro), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gill, Charlie, 2013-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gilpin, Hank, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Glasgow, Andrew, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Grafe, Steven L. / National Cowboy and Western Heritage Museum, 2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER0001-ER0002. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Little Rock Exhibition Installation, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.091 Gigabytes 51 computer files (Box ER0001)
  - Little Rock Exhibition, People, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.083 Gigabytes 67 computer files (Box ER0002)
  - Green, Bill, 1995-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Grove, Scott, 2006-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - H, 1955-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hanes, Phil, 1977-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
    Includes draft of "How to Get Anyone to Do Anything."
  - Hanson, Bobbie, 1972-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Herman, Lloyd, 1993-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hogbin, Stephen, 1982-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Horn, John and Robyn, 2004-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hosaluk, Michael, 1994-2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hucker, Tom, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - I-J, 1983-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Joseph, Wendy, 1998-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - K, 1990-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kagan, Vladimir, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kamm, Sonny and Gloria, 2003-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Kaufman, Rob, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Kelzer, Kim, 1998-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kohler, Jack Shiek, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - L, 1981-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Lavine, John, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Leopold Lawrence Interiors, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Letter to the Editor by Bennett, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Lewis, Andrew and Ginny, 1977-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Lewis, Sydney and Frances, 1978-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Lipofky, Marvin, circa 1984-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Loeser, Thomas, 2001-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lourie, Miles, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Lueckenhausen, Helmut, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Lyons Law Firm Regarding Bennett as Expert Witness, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - M, 1964-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Makepeace, Jenny, 1988-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Maloof, Sam, 1978-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Marlowe, Jack and Sue, circa 1994-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Marsh Gallery, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Maruyama, Wendy, 1983-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Meredith Gallery, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Milne, Jerry and Ann, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mondale, Joan, 1979-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Moore, Isabell, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - N, 1997-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Neff, Bob, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Neuman, Irving, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Neuman, Ursula, 1988-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - O, circa 1970-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Oberhaus, Patricia and Peter Neufeld, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Orr, Lee, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - P, 1985-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Paley, Albert, 1995-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Palmer, Robert, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Peteran, Gord, 1998-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Pieroborn, Peter, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Podmaniczky, Michael, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - R, 1975-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Rasmussen, Bob and Bernadette, 1973-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Riley, Cheryl R., 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Ritter, Dan and Armande, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Root, Michael, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - S, 1989-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Saxe, Dorothy and George, 1999-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Schwarcz, June, 1999-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sekimachi, Kay and Bob Stocksdale, 1999-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Paul, 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stals, Carol, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stocksdale, Doug and Joy, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Students, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Swiatecki, Wladyslaw, 1983-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - T-V, 1974-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Theiss, Vernon Regarding Reception for Janet Koplos, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Trapp, Ken, 2002-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - W, 1984-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Walter, Brendan, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Warren Martin, Julie, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Weiner, Sam (Evangeline Tabasco), 1978-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Wheatley, Sue, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Whitman, Marina, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wiggers, John, 2004-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wiley, Hugh, Regarding, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Alan, 1989-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wineland, Scot, Regarding, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Wood, Phil, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woodshop News Magazine, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Wornick, Ron, 1997-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - X-Z, 1997-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - First Name Only, 1974-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Unidentified, 1964-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Exhibition Files, 1979-2017; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.4 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  Arrangement
  The files are arranged in rough chronological order by exhibition year.
  The exhibitions documented in the series date from 1980 to 2016 and include files for exhibitions of Bennett's work, as well as exhibitions of pieces from his personal art collection. The files contain correspondence, artwork lists and prices, loan forms, artist statements, and printed exhibition material.
  - California Woodworking (1980-1981), Oakland Museum, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Chairs (1986), San Francisco International Airport, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Wendell Castle / Garry Knox Bennett / Fred Baier (1987), Alexander F. Milliken Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Chair Affair (1994), Oakland Museum, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Garry Knox Bennett, 100 Lamps (1996-1997), Peter Joseph Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - A Celebration of Sierra Woods: Objects of Art and Utility (1997), North Columbia Schoolhouse Cultural Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Smoke and Mirrors (1997), American Society of Furniture Artists, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Emma 2000 Collaboration (2000), University of Saskatchewan, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Horizons 2000 (2000), Lynn Tendler Bignell Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Contemporary Studio Case Furniture: The Inside Story (2002), Elvehjem Museum of Art, 1996-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Materials and Contemporary Illusions: Innovations in Lathe Turning (2002), Lynn Tendler Bignell Gallery, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Sansar 20th Anniversary Candlestick Show (2002), Sansar Gallery, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Annual Exhibition and Sale of Fine Contemporary Craft Objects (2002-2003), Museum of Craft and Folk Art, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - A Tribute to Rude Osolnik: An Exhibition of Contemporary Turned Wood (2003), Kentucky Museum of Arts and Design, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Turned Multiples III (2003), Craft Alliance (St. Louis), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Corporal Identity - Body Language, 9th Triennial (2003), MAD / Germany, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - The Eclectic Electric (2003), Function and Art (Chicago), 2003-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - "Furniture for Sex" (2003), John Elder Gallery, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Local Artists Exhibition (2003), Jack London Mail, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - The Right Stuff: A Juried Exhibition of Upholstered Furniture (2003), Furniture Society, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)